These codes simulate the simple alloy PFC model as described in the text in section 9.2. They are structured in modular form, and students an encouraged to build more complex codes using this structure. The file "manager.f" is the highest level of control, co-ordinating, so to speak, the sequence to calls to to solvers, initializations, etc. The module solver_mod.f90 contains the  solver routines. The module util_mod.f90 contains functions called upon to do various i/o.

To compile the codes into an executable, type: "make"
To run, type ./<name_of_executable>

This code uses explicit finite differencing and can run on a single processor.  Go to the directory "AlloyPFC_C_parallel" for a parallel version.